(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T22:54:23.607635",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
...obvious, time's a-wasting...
...so, don't you really wanna do it?
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be.
Sometimes it feels like you're playing my guitar...
It's so, not so predictable, they can see what I can see, but...
Get back, get back!
掃き溜めで希望を
Gathering hope in this dumpsite,
Let's just crash!
積み上げていくんだ 頂きから高らかに笑え
We will pile it up and laugh out loud from the top!
Lose control,
美しき理想を
our beautiful ideals...
不完全な世界で
In this incomplete world,
ステップ重ねた光
the light formed by repeated steps.
脈打つ鼓動 誰にもなれない言葉を紡いでよ
With a pulsing heartbeat, spin words that can belong to no one else.
...deep black.
We fall, we break,
we drown in fire.
Lost inside this dark desire.
Sorrow 溶かす 未来のMercy
Sorrow dissolves, the Mercy of the future.
色のない世界の中に
Inside this colorless world.
戻ってきて
Come back to me.
Show me what you're gonna say. What's your problem?
通る人 あたしが迷う
People pass by, and I am lost.
When the tower crashes down,
when the world caves under my pressure, there'll be no one to save.
巡る巡る 運命に逆らって
Spinning, spinning, defying our fate,
出会い 想いを通わせた
we met and connected our feelings.
The strangers I followed with stars in...
So I keep on waiting, wanting, thinking...
you're someone you're not, reaching, longing, changing.
Oh, I can't be someone else,
despite it all, my mind has become my hell.
With no escape, hoping in the dark, but still...
クラクラするでしょ？
You're getting dizzy, right?
フラフラするでしょ？
You're feeling lightheaded, right?
ほら ほら 遠くの 空 空 そうでしょ FLASH BANG!
Look, look at the distant sky, sky, right? FLASH BANG!
And this morning...
maybe I'll turn around, never knowing if I never try.
夢をみるたび
Every time I dream,
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I end up thinking about the meaning of my birth.
ああ 美しい 青い...
Ah, beautiful blue...
...fall, we break,
we drown in fire.
Lost inside this dark desire.
What's up, all you deadbeats!
Welcome to DISASTERPIECE Release! ようこそ！
Welcome to DISASTERPIECE Release! Welcome!
たくさん楽しもうね！ Let's go! Come on!
Let's have tons of fun! Let's go! Come on!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, you got eyes and ears, but you don't look or listen!
In other words, you're useless, every last one of ya!
And that's why I'm gonna send you all to hell, all of humanity!
声援背負い 颯爽と登場
Carrying your cheers, making a dashing entrance,
そういうんじゃねぇ
it's not like that.
I'm just the type you'd forget, so don't waste your time! Yeah, check it!
千切れ腐りかけの chain, going insane
A torn, decaying chain, going insane.
Somebody's gotta pay while I live with the pain
Laugh at me now, I'm the one you can't tame!
シリアスな shit, lemme shake it up
Serious shit, let me shake it up.
Do what I want, shit, gotta reckon ya
Do what I want, shit, gotta reckon with you.
Got a thirst for the worst lookin' 馬鹿な cheap-ass
Got a thirst for the worst, looking like a stupid cheap-ass.
Silly bakka, silly ba
Silly fool, silly fool.
Silly ass-looking shit, gotta shake it up
Wanna be lookin' freaks, all they do is talk
Wanna-be looking freaks, all they do is talk.
Getcha head out ya ass, like, what you got, huh?
Get your head out of your ass, like, what do you got, huh?
毎度 毎度 神頼み (uh, la-la)
Praying to God every single time (uh, la-la).
免罪せんわ そんな奴に (許し乞うたら？)
There's no absolution for someone like you (why don't you beg for forgiveness?).
あー、もう情状酌量の余地なし
Ah, there's no room for extenuating circumstances anymore.
即死刑、はい
Immediate death penalty, yes.
地獄までお逝きなさい
Go straight to hell.
Let's riot!
メラメラ burning all day
Burning bright all day.
真夏の楽園
Midsummer paradise.
メラメラ 妬かれて
Burning with jealousy.
灰になるまで
Until we turn to ashes.
メロメロにさせて
Making you fall head over heels.
さぁ踊り狂っちゃって
Now, dance like crazy.
火炙りパラダイス
Burnt-at-the-stake paradise.
Go up and down
Silly bakka, silly ba
Silly fool, silly fool.
シリアスな shit, lemme shake it up
Serious shit, let me shake it up.
Do what I want, shit, you know what I got
Might be the pinnacle of cynical but first keep the mic hot
And may I just remind you
Act a fool, death's gotta fine you
Eh, dum-di-dum-dum-de
Da-da-dum-de
考えとこうぜ
Let's think about it.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
C-A-double L, you already know
C-A-L-L, you already know.
Scythe at the ready, slow and steady, give 'em a show
Scythe at the ready, slow and steady, give them a show.
They wanna get real close, can't learn to let go
Try 'n' dance with her, answer to, look out below
Try and dance with her, answer to, look out below.
Slaying to the beat, paint the street redder than rose
Slaying to the beat, paint the street redder than a rose.
And slam 'em back 'til the sun rise and heaven's closed
And slam them back till the sun rises and heaven's closed.
Sleepin' 'til the next night, y'all know where we go
Sleeping until the next night, y'all know where we go.
Believe I still keep the tight shinigami flow
Believe I still keep the tight Grim Reaper flow.
Alright?
メラメラ burning all day
Burning bright all day.
真夏の楽園
Midsummer paradise.
メラメラ 妬かれて
Burning with jealousy.
灰になるまで
Until we turn to ashes.
メロメロにさせて
Making you fall head over heels.
Uh, 冥土の土産に舞う
Uh, dancing as a souvenir for the underworld.
That is all about
ほらまだまだ足りない
Look, it's still not enough.
Let's riot!
メラメラ burning all day
Burning bright all day.
真夏の楽園
Midsummer paradise.
メラメラ 妬かれて
Burning with jealousy.
灰になるまで
Until we turn to ashes.
メロメロにさせて
Making you fall head over heels.
さぁ踊り狂っちゃって
Now, dance like crazy.
火炙りパラダイス
Burnt-at-the-stake paradise.
Go up and down
Spent all day beneath the sun, sun, sun, sun
Sub is blasting' out, dan-dan-dan-dan
I don't care, sing out, la-la-la-la
One night this time, you don't gotta run, run
愛は痛いもんさ 苦痛ない 苦痛ない
Love is a painful thing, but there's no pain, no pain.
灼熱に飛び込んで give it to ya, give it to ya
Dive into the scorching heat, give it to you, give it to you.
Ahem, みなさん！
Ahem, everyone!
You got the rest
Mori's in the building so you know you're already dead, woo!
Chi-chikka, chi-chikka
地獄までお逝きなさい
Go straight to hell.
メラメラ burning all day
Burning bright all day.
真夏の楽園
Midsummer paradise.
メラメラ 妬かれて
Burning with jealousy.
灰になるまで
Until we turn to ashes.
メロメロにさせて
Making you fall head over heels.
さぁ踊り狂っちゃって
Now, dance like crazy.
火炙りパラダイス
Burnt-at-the-stake paradise.
Go up and down
メラメラ burning all day
Burning bright all day.
真夏の楽園
Midsummer paradise.
メラメラ 妬かれて
Burning with jealousy.
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure
There'll be no one to save
Where is your pride, your human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
Now all that remains is delusion and decay
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals
We're not equals
You're just confused
Lightning never strikes twice in the same spot
So, go ahead and run up on me till you get your shot
I see the weapon that you're hiding, come on, ready or not
Another life and you would never give a second thought
Thinking your pride's different than mine
Ticking all your vital signs off
But we still got...
...protect all our friends from our enemies
Wouldn't you agree? Ha!
Forged in fires of hell, God can't betray you
If I'm a fallen angel, what does that make you?
I'm not debasing myself to see the same view
When it's your pride on the line, no one can save you from mine
We're not rivals
We're not equals
Thank you for coming today, everyone. It's over!
No, no, no! We're back, we're back.
Just some technical difficulties.
Staff's on the beats. Everyone calm down, it's fine, it's fine, we're okay.
Welcome, welcome!
Hey, you know what? It fits, it fits in the theme of the show...
...that there'd be some technical issues.
So it can't be perfect, right? But I'm looking at your comments right now.
And thank you, by the way, to Shiori for the raid, as well. Hope the outfit reveal went super good.
Hi, Dead Beats!
Hello!
We're here! We're here!
We're finally at the Disaster-piece venue.
And I'm reading your comments, but there might be a little bit of lag, so sorry about that.
Anyway, check it out!
I've got a special, I've got my own special mic that is definitely what I'm using to talk and not the headset.
But check it out.
I'll show it, I'll show it to you closer later.
I've got... Oh! Hello! Liz is here too! Amazing! Senpai, woo-hoo!
Thank you!
Welcome to Disaster Show, everyone!
Disaster-piece is out at long last! Hooray!
We did it, we finally got here!
And now, I'm going to do some songs for you guys.
Wow! Oh, Akaspa, I can't read it right now, but I'll have to read them later. Thank you so much!
The new art style is so nice?
This is some Unreal-powered, Dead Beats! Unreal power!
It's stunning, isn't it?
I bet you want to get a closer look, and maybe get some screenshots of Mori Calliope's face.
So let me show you. Staff-san is holding a special camera, and...
いたします！ おお！
Let's do this! Oh!
Hey, hey!
Hold on, I think this is my normal hand. Oh...
All right, I'm going to take some... I'm going to get some good...
...good reaction, good reactions for you guys. Hold on a second.
Here I go.
Check this, check this, check this shit out.
はあ！
Haa!
I'm being silly.
I'm being silly because I need time to chill right now.
"You sound amazing, Calli." I'm doing my best!
Ooh-wee, and the outfit, too! Look at how shiny!
Shiny!
It just, it looks so good! And my face...
...my face looks good, too.
Oh gosh, I'm, I'm still not used to holding the camera though...
...so I'm, I'm trying to make it perfect.
But I might have to edit things a little bit. You might have to edit it later.
Hold on. No, I got this. Okay.
RTX on.
Very realistic. I can wink. Hold on, here I, here I go.
Here, wait, hold, hold on, I got this.
I suck at this.
That's okay though, that's okay.
It's, it's fine if it's not perfect.
I think I can wink. Check this out.
がんばれ。
Hang in there.
Close enough.
It looks good, and look, behind us we got the, the track...
...from the "Let's Just Crash" MV.
And we've got Challenger's car behind me.
And we've also got King's car as well.
Um, and then, well, you Deadbeats...
...you're all on your way to the next stage, so you're not there yet.
Um, but let me show you my mic.
マイク見せたいから。
Because I want to show you my mic...
急がなきゃ。
...I have to hurry.
Okay, check it out, check out the mic. This is the special Mori Calliope mic...
...that was made specially for... isn't it cool?
Look at how sick! The red and the, the roses...
I'm obsessed.
I'm obsessed with it, so...
...anyway, that's, that's what's going on.
That's what's going on, Deadbeats.
"What is the actual future of Hololive?"
Well, I mean, the technology will only get better and better, so...
...anyway, this is exciting. Uh, you guys want to see some more songs?
Um, also buy the album!
I'm, I'm all out of shape. I feel like MCs, I'm like good...
...when it's an actual live, like in a venue...
...but then if it's like this, I screw up a lot, so...
...oh well.
New merch? Uh, not neces... well, I mean, this... oh, you're talking about the mic?
You want the mic as merchandise?
I'll think about it.
Not a bad idea, I think P-san's listening to that, so I'll have to talk to her about it later.
Welcome to the future!
But anyway, Deadbeats...
...I gotta do a quick costume change and scene change...
...so let's get out of here, and I'll sing some more songs...
...and meet up with you hither and thither.
That's probably the wrong word to use in that situation, but...
...thank you, staff-san!
All right, I'll catch you guys there.
Time for a... henshin!
Time for a... transformation!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
特別な物語に 勝ち取るアイデンティティ
In my unique story, I'll claim my identity
荒れ狂った時代を変える強さを
With the strength to change this raging era...
時に伴う情けなささえ武器にしよう
...I'll turn even the occasional weakness into my weapon.
Jump!
感情はノンフィクションで喜怒哀楽
My emotions are non-fiction, with all their joys and sorrows
一心同体 一切合切が勝負
As one body and soul, everything is a showdown
失敗も成功も味わえ ワンダーランド
Taste both failure and success in this wonderland
ゴールデンバディ
Golden Buddy!
意味なんてないような 世界で
In a world that seems to have no meaning
偶然交差した光
A light that crossed paths by chance
脈打つほど誰にもなれない
Dizzyingly unique, I can't be anyone else
言葉を紡いでゆこう
Let's keep weaving our words together
運命じゃないよ 小さな勇気一つだけで
It's not fate, with just a single spark of small courage...
強気に行こうよ
...let's go forward strong!
ハートを焦がそう 二人ならやれるさ
Let's burn our hearts, we can do this together!
Go back-to-back, no matter what
追ってももがいても逃げだすブラインドスポット
Even if I chase it, that blind spot slips away
立ち違えとく蜘蛛の糸パス
We trade places, passing on a spider's thread
Shut out 誰も邪魔できないこのルート
Shut out! No one can interfere with this route
1、2、3通りだったらルーザー
If it's one, two, or three patterns, you're a loser
うざいくらい遠くに行こう
Let's go annoyingly far away
ハートが違うから だったら違うループ
Our hearts are different, so let's try a different loop
繋いだループ 満ちるラインは無限に
The connected loop, filling the line infinitely
アレグレットに満ちるメロディ
A melody full of allegretto
揺れる身 強く飲むグラス
A swaying body, taking a strong gulp of a glass
盛大に笑えばいいさ
It's fine to just laugh out loud!
才能を運ぶグラデーション
A gradation carrying talent
どうせなら狂おしいくらいにしたいよ
If anything, I want to make it crazy
初めてのマイノリティ 狂う覚悟を
For my first minority, the readiness to go mad
敗者と勝者のドロー、ドロー、ゴー！
The draw between the loser and the winner, draw, draw, go!
弾き出した不条理なパズル
The absurd puzzle we spun out
振り払え 共に勝利
Shake it off, victory together!
不釣り合いな 二人ならやれるさ
Unbalanced, but the two of us can do it!
抱いて
Embrace it!
勝ち取るはアイデンティティー
Winning back my identity
あれやこれやと 手を替え品を替え
With this and that, changing hands and methods
どきりと胸を刺す激情 感情はノンフィクションで
A sudden passion piercing my chest, emotions are non-fiction
喜怒哀楽 一心同体 一切合切の衝動
Joy, anger, sorrow, and pleasure, acting as one, all impulses together
失敗も成功も味わえ 我らゴールデンバディ
Savor both failure and success, we are the golden buddies
誰にもなれない
We can't be anyone else
ミームされた現実に囚われて
Trapped in a memed reality
This life where we're stuck taking chances
飽き飽きしたんだろ
You're sick and tired of it, aren't you?
We're living in a world with no direction
Reach out with our light 'til we make a connection
Tearing the walls apart, facing it all, side by side
Once again, it's us against the world
なめんなよ ほんとの秘密キャストさ
Don't underestimate us, we're the true secret cast
本物の凄さ見せるから
Because we'll show you the real deal
圧倒的絶頂 アンバランスを
Overwhelming climax, dance to the unbalance
踊れ！
Dance!
So just how far could I go?
I think I already know
That view that I wanna see
A place in history that's mine
I don't know why we're always side by side, but worlds apart
It's trial by fire, I'm fighting for a place where we can breathe
When spite takes over, I might just take it out on you
'Cause you're too good to be true
Struggling but carrying on
I'll go where nobody has gone
I'm searching again and again and again for something only I can do
Asking why I can't be someone else
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark, but still in my heart
Your words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go, but I can't erase you
I'm following behind, but I won't chase you
I'm swallowing my pride until the time that I can face you
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough, but I'll keep on writing
A story that's evolving from the day that I decided I'm alone
I don't belong anywhere anymore, it was my decision
I'm gonna break down the door to your heart without your permission
There was nothing that could make me stay
Remember it like it was yesterday
Hanging onto every word you'd say
What if I'd walked away?
How can I still carry on
Someday when you're finally gone?
I'm searching again and again and again for something only I can do
The truth is...
I can't be someone else, despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark, but still in my heart
My words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go, and you can't erase me
'Cause I'm the only one that could ever replace me
Igniting every line until the time that I can face me
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough, but I'll keep on writing
The story that evolved me, it's today that I'm deciding I'm alright
So just how far could I go?
I think I already know
The view that I wanna see
I still could make it in time
Ah minna-san, welcome to the next stage!
Ah everyone, welcome to the next stage!
Oh, pachipachi! Thank you for the pachipachipachi. Thank you so much! What did you guys think?
Oh, applause! Thank you for the applause. Thank you so much! What did you guys think?
And check it out!
We got this setup! Now I'm being goofy, I'm sorry.
Pachipachipachipachi they say. Thank you so much!
Applause, they say. Thank you so much!
Oh, is, is it loud out here? Sorry if there's like a, again, just lag. This is a very high quality machine we're...
...broadcast to all of you, so...
there might be a bit of lag.
But I'm happy that I can read some of your comments in real time.
Thank you so much, you guys.
Makes me very happy, much, much, much. Thank you.
Oh, but we might, we might need to refresh the...
...the chat because now it has stopped moving.
Anyway, in the mean- Oh, there it goes. There it goes.
Oh, wow. I think it just exploded when Ira entered the chat.
Anyway...
Thank you so much, you guys.
I hope you guys have been liking the new songs.
Memento was one of the new songs that I wrote.
I wish I could go into it in a longer MC...
...or talk more about it, because there's so much I want to say...
...about that song, um, but it's...
It's, oh, oh, hold on, hold on.
I'm frozen, I'm frozen in place!
Okay. We're, we're good. We're good.
大丈夫。ごめん、ザ・ワールド。
All good. Sorry, "The World" time stop.
No problem, no problem. Here, for now, though...
...instead of going into talking about the lyrics, which I'll probably do...
...during the next, during the next stream...
...we'll find some time before or after I play a game...
...and then I'll talk about the songs.
Um, until then...
Hang on, hold on a second.
You know, Kenti couldn't be here for "Gold on Balance"...
...but, you know, what I've learned from Kenti's song...
...is that fan service is very important.
I used to be really like nervous...
...about doing fansa and stuff like that...
...cuz like, I'm- I'm an embarrassed person.
But, but Kenti so easily is just like...
"Oh, like, chu chu to..." like the fan, like, wink, and like...
...I don't know, he's so good at the fansa.
And like, with no shame whatsoever.
I thought to myself, "I need to try and do some of that, too." So...
...um, I'm going to do that.
Chu!
Probably not very good at it, but anyway.
Hold on, I'll start- Oh, no, it's perfect...
...because Za Warudo...
...it stopped it for you so that you could get a, a little picture.
Watch where you're pointing that camera.
Hold on a second, I'm not pointing it anywhere suspicious.
What are you talking about?
Can I do, can I do a funny face now?
Haaaa!
Oh, no.
Anyway, um, so here's this outfit.
And it looks so high-quality, again.
Hey, you notice something about the stage?
This is the coin from the beginning of "Gold on Balance".
Dead Beats, look.
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world that seems to have no meaning...
It's the "tuuuun"...
不確かな物語に
...to an uncertain story.
Anyway...
...so check it out, hold on.
Look at how cool the stage is, by the way.
Are you checking out the stage?
Look at those, the roses, the moon.
It reminds me of when I debuted...
...from Universal Music Japan...
...and I had the moon in the background of...
...what was it, I think it was one of my debut albums.
So cool, looking very respectful.
Oh, I know.
You don't need to tell me.
I already know.
Of course.
As always.
I could put it as high as possible.
Woah, my eyes are glowing in the darkness.
What about the effects?
The effects are also so cool for this show.
I can't believe it.
We have some even more amazing stages coming up.
But if you guys haven't checked out the album yet...
...it's full of brand new songs.
Um, one of them I composed myself.
And then all the songs, all the English in my songs is written by me...
...except for maybe Cult Following, and that's it.
But that's in a different album.
So it's safe to say all the English lyrics are my own.
And then for Japanese lyrics...
...I basically tell the lyricists what I want it to be about...
...and give them like my lyrics too so they know...
...what to write about. But yeah.
So it's full of my thoughts and my feelings.
I'm going to put this one- I really don't need to keep holding this.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
But yeah, it's full of my thoughts and my feelings...
...about the world and the world around me.
And, uh, this time it's a bit darker, a bit more emotional.
But you guys know that I have a lot of emotions inside of me.
And I feel like the best way to deal with those...
...is to put them out in the world in like a productive way.
I love "Shuuden".
終電。
Last train.
That's what it means in Japanese.
I can't wait to talk more about that song, too.
That's also very close to my heart, that song.
Um, I want to say so much more...
...but I probably need to wrap it up.
"Amazing per usual." Thank you!
That's Nice_Ige. Thank you so much.
"The lyrics are all amazing." Thank you, Dead Beat!
I appreciate, I appreciate all of you. Thank you.
We'll have- we have some more to do here, so...
...I can't go on forever.
This is a very long MC, so...
...let's do another henshin, and...
...ikuzo!
...let's go!
Don't look back
Look forward
Find something you can move toward
Don't look back
I was slipping then falling, kept on looking for something to bring me up
Ask me, no such thing as hope
Ask me, there's no such thing as hope
Walk the thin ice and it shattered to pieces
More than a reach, it seems all my chances decrease
Perhaps a winner but cynical as I just might be
Our end is still unwritten, I think I'm about to break free
My limits closing around me, they're sounding less and less real
Because my heart is beating louder than the fear that I fear
My mind's already made up, not afraid of unreal
Live the dream, looking for my screen scene, so I can walk the border
Used to look for perfection, now it's progress
Every dues paid, part of the process
In this moment
Maybe it's all for last
Not knowing if I'll never try
Changing faces
Enveloped in moonlight
I can see stars now
Running through an endless sky
Only one moment for you to live how you wanted
Don't look back
Find something you can move toward
I fight another day, these battles inside and outside
Have all that I wanted, why am I still unsatisfied?
Lost taxis and street signs, the city mirroring my mind
Alleys to level up forever to find
Get a world to climb, I was always told but they were like, 'Nah'
Now it's up to me to rise
Give them a little surprise, my mind never slides
Always riding high, thrive on this lovely hate, my future's sky high
Outrunning all my shadows, still the worn-out shoes
With everything to gain, even more to give up and lose
This time you gotta choose, no excuse, tired of sleeping, gotta move
Envisioning tomorrows that are too good to refuse
Reddest of skies writing
But I lost my aim
More things change
The more they stay the same
Burning strife
And chain
This pain will be
My strength
In this moment
Maybe it's all for last
Not knowing if I'll never try
Changing faces
Enveloped in moonlight
I can see stars now
Guiding me to find
For this moment
We're no longer broken
Never leaving love behind
This morning
I wake up to sunshine
Living with resolve now
Running with a fearless stride
Only one moment for you to live how you wanted
Don't look back
Find something you can move toward
見渡した 君がため
I looked around for your sake
花咲いた 明日は雨
Flowers bloomed, tomorrow it rains
為せば成る何事も 終わりのないゲーム
Anything is possible in this endless game
転がるままに 押し通せる
I can push forward, letting things roll
迷信だってくらべりゃ 妄想念慮呼び合うら
Compared to superstition, we call out to delusional thoughts
混声中 達にする 瞑想にトラベル
Mixing voices, reaching meditation on our travel
トラブル キャピタライズ
Trouble, capitalize
インフィニティ 噛み締んで 本当に 本当に
Truly, truly biting down on infinity
上昇して行く者を 一生 休止
Suspending those who rise forever
Underneath the blue skies, still choose to sing because I refuse to die
Grit teeth and try to look past the pain
But these flowers are watered with acid rain, can't change belief
I tried and tried, my grief has seen that I left behind
And if I can find a place to rest our minds
I can live with it a lifetime
沈んでいく黄昏を 見つめて
Watching the twilight sink
I got a feeling that I'll still sing anyway
最悪を覆す 未来の上
On top of the future that overturns the worst
未来の上
On top of the future
迷わない 信じたい 最後の合図に
I won't hesitate, I want to believe in the final sign
焦げ付くほどの 奔流を味わって
Savoring the torrent that burns
Hello, hello, 今宵のデイドリーマー
Hello, hello, tonight's daydreamer
Let's maintain
Attention, chatter, clap, click, clack
妄想 粘度 病 溢だく
Delusion, viscosity, sickness, corruption...
来世中 達成する 成し遂げる
Achieving and accomplishing it in the next life,
Travel, trouble, careful lives
Sacrifice the false cards
Bloody fangs, cats hide their claws
Nobody's ever truly what they seem
With the limelight gleam to conceal the flaws
Can't escape the scrolling, it takes a toll on me
Dead and thus still looping, holding me
Did it even matter in the end that I held out?
Sorry, I could never be the god of the souls to be
So to speak, an island fool
Living out the role I was told to be
Only old and free in a matter of centuries
Wonder if there was a point to me
Was thinking for sure I belong on my own
But now, thought I found a place to belong
People I can't live without...
Follow me please, don't go, no double-take, I don't care!
暗い闇 消えないで そばにいて
In the dark night, don't fade away, stay by my side.
Don't get swept away, kept dead, now there's no way
遠い星、描いた、ただ踊ってたい
A distant star I imagined, I just want to keep dancing.
Hello, hello, 今宵のインソムニア
Hello, hello, tonight's insomnia.
Let's maintain
In a world where nothing is certain
Except that someday we will say goodbye
I want to keep my eyes on the sky...
育みたい、な、私達...
I want to nurture us...
TENSHOU!
天を穿つ未来の結び
A knot of the future piercing the heavens,
祈る主 新体制の愛
a praying lord, love of a new regime,
焦げ付くほどの放流、溢ろう
scorching discharge, let it overflow.
Hello, hello, 今宵のデイドリーム
Hello, hello, tonight's daydream.
Let's maintain
Tenshou! We're changing the state!
Tenshou! We're starting the party!
Tenshou! We're getting the S-S-S-S-Superfire!
Tenshou! We're changing the state!
Tenshou! We're starting the party!
Tenshou! We're getting the S-S-S-S-Superfire!
あー、いやいや、皆さん！うー！
Ah, yeah, yeah, everyone! Woo!
How was that? Tenshou and Mercy, you know.
Writing that song reminded me, yes, I still can write songs that are extremely difficult to perform live. Let's go!
Some things never change, Dead Beats. But hey, how about the tech for this concert?
Hold on, are you guys seeing this Sakura behind me? Like, the detail!
Oh, hold on, so- again, the Sakura tree is very powerful! It's- it's such a- such a big item and so detailed.
Sometimes I stop moving. That's okay, it doesn't matter. Woo! ぱちぱちぱち！
Sometimes I stop moving. That's okay, it doesn't matter. Woo! Clap, clap, clap!
That was, like, a thousand out of ten, nailed it, let's go.
ありがとうございます。It is clean, drink water.
Thank you so much. It is clean, drink water.
That's a really good idea.
水、水、水！
Water, water, water!
I gulp, I gulp. The invisible water.
But, I mean, if you guys think back to Phantasm, I see a lot of you guys talking about, like, oh, the production, the quality is so crazy.
It's very powerful stuff going on around here, and they really knocked it out of the park with this.
I just have so much thanks to give to my staff. Be sure, we have a little credit roll at the end that will play, and, you know, that's my staff, and big ups to them.
But remember the Phantasm concert, you guys, that we did, the little mini live for the release of Phantasm, which was really cool.
That already had, like, the- the echoes of the beginning of even better quality for these shows, right?
Well, can you imagine what the next is gonna look like?
I mean, if this- if this looks like this right now, I mean, can you imagine where we go from here?
I mean, it's really exciting to think about. 20 years from now, Dead Beats, 20 years from now, who knows.
I probably will be as detailed as that Sakura tree. But- but don't worry, it won't be too much, it'll still feel like me. I'll make sure about that.
This is already kind of toeing the line, I think.
But I'd love to, like, move my face a little bit more, and stuff like that. Would be more dramatic if leaves were scattering around.
That's a good point! However, Dead Beat, you say that. If Sakura was falling right now, I think that- I think that every PC in this studio would catch on fire. Great idea, though.
自撮りタイム！
Selfie time!
Okay, here we go. Now I'm using this camera again. Woah, okay.
You guys can get- I'm backing up, I'm backing up. A bit of a closer look...
That Sakura tree behind, that's- that's- that is 3D. Hold on, I got- I got this.
That- that is 3D.
They're laughing, they're laughing, you're laughing at me! Stop it!
Stop!
Someday, I'll be able to make an angrier face at you. So, get ready for that.
That's another thing to look forward to, Dead Beats, when Mori Calliope can make an angrier face at you.
Talking to you.
Ooh, check out my nails.
You think cats hide their claws?
Claws.
Hey, this is a cute little screenshot, too.
I heard from my Pi-san, my Pi-san showed a little piece of paper
I heard from my producer, who showed a little piece of paper
to me that said that
#DisasterShow entered... entered the trends in USA.
Thank you so much for that!
Dead Beats, keep it coming.
And some folks are like, "Mori, I can't believe that this is free!"
Of course it's free, 'cause I know... I know that the majority of you guys bought the album,
so it might as well be free.
And if you didn't buy it, you've at least been streaming it,
so it just feels... it just feels right, I guess, to do what I can
to make it worth it to you guys
even more, even more so.
Hi! You guys remember this outfit?
It's a little on the older side, but check it out.
You guys remember, right, from my very first solo show,
New Underworld Order?
It's looking good, right?
I'm looking good?
Hi.
Trying to get as much camera screen time as I can.
Buy the album, buy the album! Say the Dead Beats. おねがいします！
Buy the album, buy the album! Say the Dead Beats. Please!
If you could, I'd be very happy.
Whoa, this is kind of a cool shot with the sakura!
Whoa, this is kind of a cool shot with the cherry blossoms!
My eyes are glowing in the darkness. Hey there, hi.
Huaaa!
I'll keep trying to make silly faces, though. That's something that will never change about me.
This is a screenshot moment!
Whenever it stops, it means it's a screenshot moment. Maybe.
Anyway, it's time to move on because I still have a couple songs
to sing for you guys. I think this one will end up being longer than PhantomIME, which is a good thing.
I get to sing even more for you.
What songs will they be? I wonder.
ありがとう、スタッフさん！
Thank you, staff members!
And, uh, yeah. So...
I guess it's about time that we move on to the next spot.
Looking good!
Thanks, Dead Beats. You want to see my high kicks? I've been working on them.
よいしょ！
Hup!
And...
よいしょ！
Hup!
My high kicks.
よいしょ！
Hup!
Next year, I'm going to kick even higher. You'll see.
Anyway, some randomness right there.
Let's go.
Next 変身！
Next transformation!
いくぞ！
Let's go!
I put my last illusions behind
Still, you're creeping through my thoughts tonight
Now, I know it's only skin deep
Drawn like moths to flame inside your
heat, heat, heat
Considered myself fine, but I'm crossing every line
Drunk on love that's not mine
Heaven sent you way too late, kiss of death and take the bait
Past lives and loaded dice, white lies and alibis
Fingers tracing edge of sin
a medicine I never swallowed right
Still no enemy to fight, not in this light
Stolen whispers, don't ask and don't tell
Step in my world, and welcome to hell
Sinking down in your deep black
We fall, we break
We drown in fire
Lost inside in this dark desire
No love, no faith
Just you and I
Dancing 'til the end of time
Ba-la-la-la-la-la, la-la-la
End of time, end of time
End of time
Ba-la-la-la-la-la, la-la-la
La-la-la-la-la-la, la-la-la
I still blame myself for this hate
Shame that overflows and never dissipates
I let words unsaid rot slowly
Tainted and unholy
No, don't say it, watch, wait
Cold steel pressed against your neck
Ba-la-la-la-la-la-la
End of time, end of time
End of time
One last breath before we die
The sight of you intoxicates
Say your prayers, passed the time to confess
...when it takes us to rest,
Six feet under, side by side.
We fall, we break, we drown in fire,
lost inside this dark desire.
No love, no fate, just you and I,
dancing through the end of time.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la...
Ashes fall from blackened skies,
all that's left is you and I.
Drowned inside this love tonight.
End of time, end of time, end of time.
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though,
my heart's beating to your song.
Oh, yeah?
Then go hurry up, Orpheus, time's a-wasting!
Show me what you really wanna do.
Another late night, aimless dreaming,
then the day starts to call.
Still got like a million deadlines, drinking red wine,
back up against the wall.
I got my headphones on, walk home is long,
dragging feet like I'm born to lose.
Till somehow they're tapping along to you-know-who's song,
a melody I can't refuse.
Am I lost in the style? Get you off of my mind,
keeping silent when I don't feel the shame or guilt.
I know I get a little carried away,
but we got music when there are no more words to say.
Is it my heart that's speaking when you look this way?
Can you hear me singing from the stage when you feel the same?
Now I'm in distress, you got me possessed, I might be obsessed,
so let me get a little something off my chest, look...
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though,
my heart's beating to your song.
Oh, yeah?
Then hurry up, Orpheus, time's a-wasting!
Show me what you really wanna do.
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be.
Sometimes it feels like you're playing that guitar
for me and only me.
Critics so loud, so predictable,
they can say what they wanna say.
We're gonna wind up a star!
Just discard my fear, my wonder,
I wonder if it's enough.
Because I'm on the line when I'm implying
you're all that I've been thinking of.
Maybe they'll call me delusional,
baby, this could be real love.
Give me one chance and I'll take...
dance the night away!
Now it's a game that I've played before, but with the way the scene changed,
there is nothing you can blame me for.
I'm talking TV screens, magazines, seeing you in a couple of dreams,
pictures up on every padded wall and floor.
Always talking about no time to desire a lover,
so why'd you paint your nails up in my favorite color?
I got an attitude just when it comes to you,
see our reality is kind of slipping out of view.
Though I never lost in the groove of somebody new,
if it's devotion you're after, I'm staying true.
So are you noticing me noticing you noticing me noticing losing,
but there's not a lot I guarantee.
Is it my heart that's speaking when you look this way?
Can you hear me singing from the stage when you feel the same?
You're strumming next to me, I'm in ecstasy,
and for the rest of the week, I'm depression free.
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though,
my heart's beating to your song.
Oh, yeah?
Then hurry up, Orpheus, time's a-wasting!
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be.
As long as you keep playing that guitar...
Woo!
Critics so loud, so predictable,
they can say what they wanna say.
We're gonna wind up a star!
Just discard my fear, my wonder,
I wonder if it's enough.
Because I'm on the line when I'm implying
you're all that I've been thinking of.
Maybe they'll call me delusional,
baby, this could be real love.
Give me one chance and I'll take...
dance the night away!
Hey! Hey! Come on!
So let's blow this joint, and if the feeling's right,
then we can make a little music of our own tonight. Come on!
Hey! Hey!
Why are you walking away? I got a lot to say,
guess I'll save it for the next one.
Woo!
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though,
my heart's beating to our song.
Oh, yeah?
So hear me out, Orpheus, thinking next time,
I'll show you what I really wanna do.
I'm back, Dead Beats! Where'd the cats go?
Hey, wait a minute, where are the weird cats at?
They were just here a second ago.
Dead Beats, check out what I can do. Hold on, get ready.
Are you ready? Check it out.
I'm obsessed with how this dress moves, Dead Beats!
Almost... let me back up a little bit. Look at how it moves.
moves, ooh, so scandalous!
Ah, don't look!
The physics are crazy!
Ah, how about those weird cats though,
doing the dance?
It was so cute! The creature...
Nice moves, thank you!
Thank you Deadbeats. Meow meow!
Oh, that was fun.
That was fun, Deadbeats!
I had such a good time with you guys today.
Actually, I mentioned to you guys my family...
My family came to glorious Nippon!
And actually we kind of celebrated the release together.
I was like, you know, sneaking around some places that were selling the album.
And then hearing my own music blasting on the speakers.
They were playing Orpheus, they were playing, uh, Golden Balance,
they were playing Let's Just Crash. And for the first time...
ever, Deadbeats,
walking around the store, I didn't feel like...
embarrassed,
which is a step in the right direction. I feel like...
I've been getting better.
Deadbeats, I hope it was fun. It was so fun.
Deadbeats, I can't even explain, uh, being able to be so proud
and say, "Look, that's my thing, they're playing my song on the speaker."
It's so cool. I mean, I went to karaoke with my little sister.
She told me that Die for You was her favorite song of mine, and Meta Meta,
which made me very happy.
Those are little sister reap's favorites.
And I sang... I sang it for her and her friends,
because they really wanted to hear and they're like, "Wow, free concert!"
It was really cool.
Um, so yeah, there was that.
What else did I want to talk about? I don't know.
I feel like, even today with... with today's show,
I feel like I'm getting more confident to do more things with my voice,
and I can do more things with my voice.
It's still a little rough and unpolished, but like, that's the point of Disasterpiece in general, right?
I'm working towards my masterpiece.
And maybe, um, it will take some time to get things exactly the way that I want.
Maybe I'll never get there, you know? But...
I'm doing more with my voice,
and even though it's new stuff and it needs polishing, um, I'm really happy...
with it.
What's... What's my favorite song? Ask the Deadbeats.
Oh... I don't know. I like them for different reasons.
The one that maybe I'm proudest of is maybe Rivals and Equals,
um, because I still... I listen to that and I'm like, "Yeah, that's really good."
But then I also really like Shuden for the lyrics as well,
probably my favorite lyrics I've written in a long time. So...
Yeah, that's right. That Deadbeats says it's about the journey.
Exactly.
I'm running out of time here, so let me get this jidori camera really quick. Hold on.
Ah, yes.
My eyes are glowing in the dark right now because we're in a dark area, but...
now I'm going to show you the skirt moving. Let's get on the red.
Can I get on the red?
Okay, I'm moving my... my che- my chest, my chest piece, which is myself, to the red. Look at the skirt.
It's kind of hard to see.
Sorry.
Doing my best over here.
Uh, maybe... maybe it's better to view from the other side. So...
look, there's the... this is the stage from Die for You MV.
And then,
you can see if we look this way, it's darkness,
and then if we look this way, it's darkness.
But it's still really cool. Oh, what... what was that?
It kind of looks like the wall that maybe leads to the hospital? I don't know.
Respectfully, of course.
Peace.
Let me... It's so... It's so dark in here.
I'll make it work.
Hi.
Hello.
It is I, Mori Calliope, and I just released a new album.
It's my best work so far.
And in Japan, we got number one album on the...
on iTunes ranking. Yay! For alternative, for alternative music.
So let's see how much further we can push. Last time I checked in US, it was... it was climbing,
it was getting high up, but you know there's lot of stiff competition there so...
so it's all good, but all good.
If we don't, if we don't reach number one, that's fine.
But I'd love for you guys to keep pushing for me, if you would like to.
Spread the... the word and keep listening in all your favorite places,
keep enjoying the album, and I will keep making...
I'll keep doing stuff that only I can do,
like writing Mori Calliope lyrics!
So... yeah.
I guess that's about it.
I want to give a special thanks to Deadbeats and to staff-san.
いつもありがとうございます。
Thank you very much as always.
My staff is the best.
Please look at the credits, so you know who to say thank you to, Deadbeats.
Uh, and yeah, posted everywhere.
Thank you. Thank you Deadbeats.
I'm... I'm reading y'all's comments. Eat the camera?
I think that's a bad idea. I think they'll get mad at me if I do that.
I think... I think it's... it's going to break things. So...
anyway, that's the end of the jidori camera.
Um, anyway, we are back here.
So, I guess that's... oh, wrong...
Like I said, I'm using a headset.
Uh, no, no, no, really. Microphone, trust, trust.
Um, but you know, with the technical stuff, there's always a little bit of magic involved, right?
In order to get the level of quality that we've got, so...
But thank you guys always for cheering for me and being excited about my work.
There is no encore because life has no encore, so sorry about that.
I know there are a lot of songs you guys want to hear me sing. The good news is...
I will be singing them soon for you on my streams.
So tune into my streams!
...my karaoke streams, and streams where I'm singing my stuff,
and future shows, if there's a song that you really want to hear. Like, I know a lot of you probably wanted to hear Shuden, for example. So...
If you want to hear it, you gotta stay tuned and come to the next one. But like I said,
life has no encore.
So, what I want you to do now is just rewatch the live.
And then go listen to the music, links in the description.
Thank you Dead Beats, always, for cheering for me.
Thank you for supporting what I do.
I'm strange,
but you know, this is really fun. I'm glad I get to do this every day.
And I put my whole heart into the new release, so...
I'll see you guys tomorrow. We're playing a game!
There's, there's a game stream tomorrow.
See you guys around.
Thanks again, everyone.
I'm your Mori, hope you'll remember me.
Peace!
DISASTER SHOW - Mori Calliope
DISASTERPIECE - Mori Calliope
Hurry up, Orpheus, time's a wasting!
Show me what you really wanna do!
Tonight, it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing that guitar for me and only me
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can't see what I can see
Let's riot!
Get back, you're trash!
掃き溜めで希望を
Finding hope in the trash heap,
Let's just crash!
積み上げていくんだ
I'll keep piling it up.
頂から高らかに笑え
Laugh out loud from the top!
Get back, you're trash!
美しき理想を...
A beautiful ideal...
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world that seems meaningless,
偶然を重ねた光
lights overlapped by chance.
脈打つ鼓動
A pulsing heartbeat,
誰にもなれない
I can't be anyone else.
言葉を紡いでよ
Spin your words.
Sinking down in your deep black...
We fall...
We break...
We drown in fire...
Lost inside this dark desire...
ハレワタレ
Clear up!
Mercy!
ナセバナルナラバ
If you can do it, do it,
惜しみのない pain
pain with no regrets.
「偽物だ！！」って
Saying "It's a fake!!"
Tell me what I'm to "not say"
What's your problem?
夜を一人 あたしが迷う
Alone in the night, I lose my way.
When thunder...
...crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure...
...there'll be no one to save.
めぐるめぐる
Going round and round...
運命に逆らって
...defying our fate,
出会いを想いを通わせた
...we shared our encounters and feelings.
Strangers I followed with star-scent
So you keep on waiting...
...wanting...
...faking you're someone you're not...
...reaching, longing, changing...
I can't be someone else
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape, or hope in the dark
But still alive in my...
クラクラ クラクラ クラクラでしょう
Dizzy, dizzy, dizzy, right?
ホロホロトークソング
Holo-Holo talk song,
そうでしょう
isn't that right?
フラッシュバング
Flash Bang!
In this moment...
Maybe it's over now...
And knowing if I never tried...
夢を見るたび
Every time I dream,
生まれてきた意味を考えてしまうの
I end up thinking about the meaning of my birth.
あぁ 美しい青い日
Ah, a beautiful blue day...
We fall...
We break...
We drown in fire...
Lost inside this dark desire...